# **Boming Zhou**

User Experience & User Interface Designer

781 - 363 - 6658 zhou.boming@gmail.com behance.net/bomingzhou Sharon, MA

## **About me:**

I am a creatively driven individual who is highly motivated in solving design problems through my skills in technology, design, and psychology with one year of experience.

My design process follows a flexible but thorough manner where I begin with research, such as competitive analysis and user interviews/surveying. User personas and journey maps are created from the information gathered, which helps create low-fidelity wireframes. After polishing the designs and going through testing phases, wireframes turn into high-fidelity prototypes through many iterations, where they can be presented and handed off.

## **Experience:**

### Optometry Office

#### **Assistant**

July 2019 - August 2019

- Greeted 10-15 visitors at service desk each day, scheduled appointments, and verified insurance coverage for services
- Organized and prepared office files
- Checked patients' insurance and managed payments

## Asian Community Development Corporation Volunteer June 2017 - August 2019

- Organized office files and analyzed data
- Analyzed exam grades and survey answers using Excel
- Assisted visitors and customers at front desk

#### **UMass Amherst**

#### **Teaching Assistant** September 2018 - December 2018

- Psychology Teaching Assistant
- Graded many assignments from students, and proctored exams
- Held office hours to assist students with material

#### Education:

#### CareerFoundry:

UX Design Program 2020 - 2021

#### University of Massachusetts Amherst:

Bachelor's of Psychology 2016 - 2020

#### **Skills:**

- User Research
- Wireframina
- Prototypina
- Usability Testing
- Aaile UX
- Designing for Accessibility
- Graphic Design

#### Tools:

- Adobe XD, Photoshop, Illustrator,
- Axure, Zeplin, Figma, Sketch
- HTML, CSS3, Javascript

#### Interests:

- Photography
- Video Editing
- Drawina
- Interior Design